http://www.halfpricebanners.com/privacy-policy

Effective June 27th, 2017
HalfPriceBanners.com, Inc. ("Company") respects Internet users' concern about the privacy of their personal information. Therefore, we have created this Privacy Policy in order to explain our practices with respect to the collection, use, and disclosure of personal and non-personal information provided by recipients of our marketing messages, visitors to our Website, and our marketing partners, advertisers, and other third parties.
If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, please contact us at support@halfpricebanners.com or call Customer Service at (866) 527-1363.
Summary
What information do we collect?
We collect information from you when you register on our site, place an order, subscribe to our newsletter, respond to a survey, or fill out a form.
We collect your email address, mailing address and phone number.
We offer a number of different payment methods. Regardless of which method you choose, we never retain, save or store your credit card information.
What do we use your information for?
We use this information to process and communicate with you regarding your order, customize your user experience and improve our customer service and Website.
How do we protect your information?
We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or enter, submit, or access your personal information including using Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and encryption when communicating with PayPal, our payment gateway.
Do we disclose any information to outside parties?
We do not share, sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information for their promotional purposes.
Collection of Information:
We collect personal information from visitors to our Website when they voluntarily provide it to us by (1) completing our registration form, (2) electing to use one of our services, or (3) contacting us (including our webmaster, customer service representatives, or other employees) by email or phone. As part of these activities, we may ask individuals to provide us with information including, but not limited to, name, physical address, email address, telephone number, and demographic information.
As part of the standard operation of our Website and the web pages that you access via hyperlinks in our online marketing campaigns ("Other Web Pages"), we may collect certain non-personal information from visitors including, but not limited to, their browser type (e.g., Chrome or Internet Explorer), operating system (e.g., Windows or Macintosh), IP address, and the domain name from which they accessed the site. In addition, we may collect information about visitors' browsing behavior, such as the date and time they visit our Website or Other Web Pages, the areas or pages of our Website and Other Web Pages that they visit, the amount of time spent viewing our Website and Other Web Pages, the number of times the visitor returns to our Website and Other Web Pages, and other click-stream data.
We may use cookies (small text files that are stored on the hard drives of visitors computers when they access our Website) to collect this information, which may be combined with visitors' personally identifiable information (such as your name, email address and IP address) to ensure that your user experience on our Site is tailored to your preferences & allow you to sign in automatically without having to re-enter your password each time.
We do not share, sell, rent, or trade personal information with third parties for their promotional purposes.
Third Party Cookies:
We may from time to time engage third parties to track and analyze non-personally identifiable usage and volume statistical information from visitors to our Site to help us administer our Site and improve its quality. Such third parties may use cookies to help track visitor behavior. Such cookies will not be used to associate individual website visitors to any personally identifiable information. We don't have access to these third party cookies. This privacy policy only governs the use of cookies by www.halfpricebanners.com.
Choices about Cookies:
You can configure your browser to accept all cookies, reject all cookies, or notify you when a cookie is set. (Each browser is different, so check the "Help" menu of your browser to learn how to change your cookie preferences.)
Please note that if you turn your cookies off, some of our services may not function properly and discount may not be applied correctly or at all.
Service Providers:
We use a third party shipping agent to send our orders. We also employ a third party agent to provide financial services that allow us to process your payments. None of these third parties are authorized to use your information for their promotional purposes.
Updating Your Personal Information:
If your personally identifiable information changes, or if you no longer desire our service, you may correct or update it by emailing our Customer Service at support@halfpricebanners.com or by contacting us (866) 527-1363 or postal mail at the contact information listed below.
You can also access your information by accessing the "Log In" on our Site and updating your information.
Disclosure of Information:
We do not share your information with any third parties for their promotional purposes. All information collected from our users is only shared with those Employees, and service providers who need access to provide you with a service. Disclosure of information may also be necessary to respond to warrants, subpoenas, or other judicial processes to provide information to law enforcement agencies, or to facilitate investigation of matters of public safety, as permitted by law.
Security:
We use industry-accepted standards to protect your information, including SSL encryption when transmitting sensitive information. We have implemented certain physical, encrypted, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect. Visitors should consider any electronic communication that they transmit to us (such as data, questions or answers, comments, suggestions, or other communications) to be non-confidential. While we take every precaution to protect your information, we cannot guarantee 100% safety and highly recommend being careful in the information you submit within emails. We will not be liable or responsible if information that belongs to an individual is intercepted and used by an unintended recipient, or is otherwise accessed and used without our written permission.
Importantly, we do not retain or record any financial information that you use to pay for orders on our website.
Opt-Out Policy:
We offer visitors to our Website the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us. If you have subscribed to our service and wish to stop receiving any future communications from us, please email us at support@halfpricebanners.com. These unsubscribe options are also included in email communications that you receive from us.
We take all reasonable measures to ensure that your unsubscribe requests are fulfilled in a timely manner. However, despite these precautions, there is always the chance that after you unsubscribe you may receive additional communications from us that may have resulted from an inadvertent technical or other processing error. If this happens, please notify us of those communications by writing to support@halfpricebanners.com and we will take immediate steps to rectify the situation.
Testimonials:
We post customer testimonials on our Website which may contain personally identifiable information such as the customer's name. We do obtain the customer's consent prior to posting the testimonial to post their name along with their testimonial. If a customer chooses to post personally-identifiable information to our website, it may be used by other users of the website to contact you. We are not responsible for the personally-identifiable information a user chooses to post to our website with their testimonial.
Children:
We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Children's Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not knowingly collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.
Third Party Websites:
Our Website and Other Web Pages that are accessible through our online marketing campaigns may contain links to other third party Websites (such as those of our advertisers), which may have privacy policies that differ from our own. We are not responsible for the activities and practices that take place on these Websites. Accordingly, we recommend that you review the privacy policy posted on any Website that you may access through our Website.
Business Transitions:
In the event that the Company or any of its assets are acquired by a third party, your personally identifiable information would be one of the transferred assets. We shall notify you of such an event by prominent notice on our site.
Changes To This Privacy Policy:
There may be times when we need to amend, modify, remove, or change various aspects of this Privacy Policy, and we reserve the right to do so at our discretion. We recommend that you revisit this Privacy Policy periodically to ensure that you are aware of our current privacy practices. Additionally, we will prominently note on our website that our Privacy Policy has been changed and provided you did not elect to no longer receive correspondence from us, you will be notified via e-mail that changes have been made to our Privacy Policy. You can be assured that any changes that we make will not be applied retroactively and that we will not materially change how we handle previously collected information without your consent. Your continued use of our services following any changes signifies your acceptance of these changes.
I Further Agree To The Below Statement:
Even if I am on a National or State DO NOT CALL List, by requesting information and contact as offered on our Websites inquiry form and submitting my contact information which may include my telephone number, the Company and affiliates are authorized to contact me by telephone at that number regarding services I have requested from the Company for the three (3) month period following date of this consent.
Questions About This Statement:
Please send all your Privacy questions or concerns to us at the address provided below.
Chat with us right now!
E-Mail Us!
E-Mail
E-Mail Us!
FAQ
Quick Question?
Here's our FAQ
FAQ
Quick Question?
* Subject to our Terms and Conditions
Quote
Pricing questions?
Request a Free Quote
Terms of Service
Privacy Policy
Return Policy
Welcome to Half Price Banners!
Get 10% off
Your First Order
We respect your privacy and do not share your personal information*
No thank you, I don't need the extra money.
Wait, wait! Come back!
Get 10% off
Your First Order
We respect your privacy and do not share your personal information*
No thank you, I don't need the extra money.
